NOOR AZIMAH BINTI AHMAD

- Kangar, Perlis, Malaysia
- noorazimahahmad2@gmail.com
- 60175286132

Profile

Name	Noor Azimah binti Ahmad	
Gender	Female	
Date Of Birth	07 Sep 1991	
Age	26 years	
Availibility	Immediately	
Marital Status	Single	
Nationality	Malaysian	
Work Permit	I am citizen	
Current Address	No. 79 RPA Batu 16, Jalan Padang Besar , 02200 Kaki Bukit, Kangar, Perlis.	
Other Address	Lot 2560, Bukit Jelutong Mukim 3, 13500 Bukit Mertajam, Pulau Pinang.	

Objective

Seeking to leverage acquired more knowledge and work experience to effectively fill any vacancies that match with my capabilities. A dedicated worker aiming to help achieve company goals and take on more responsibility as quickly as possible.

Experience

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017

Dong Hua Forwarding Agent Sdn Bhd

Position: Account Assistant

Job Description:Prepare invoicing, cash book, issue cheques and tax invoice for customers by using autoucount system. Other than that, i am also assists in preparing documents with my teammates for audit.

Sep 2016 - Mar 2017

Amza Wawasan Enterprise

Position :Clerk

Job Description:-I am responsible in attracting and screening potential candidates, employees claims and utilities bills, assist in payroll, SOCSO, EPF, updated employees attendance, preparing invoices, communicated with government agencies, updated stock, preparing company profile and performance support for tenders use.

Aug 2015 - Nov 2015

Smartrac Technology Sdn Bhd

Position :HR Trainee

Job Description: Arranged recruitment process, assist in payroll, update foreigners worker file, and assist in employees welfare.

Oct 2011 - Mar 2012

Unimap, perlis

Position: Secretary Assistant (Trainee)

Job Description:-I am responsible to provide minute of meetings, involved with company events, involved in 5S tasks, and other admin tasks being given.

Education

Jun 2013 - Oct 2016

Uitm

Major: Human Resources Management

(Grade:3.22)

Jun 2009 - Mar 2012

Universiti Teknologi Mara

Major :Office Management and Technology

(Grade :3.22)

Jan 2003 - Dec 2008

Smk Raja Puan Muda Tengku Fauziah, Perlis

Major :Pure Science and Principal of Accounting

(Grade :4A,1B,3C)

Referees

University of Technology MARA, Kedah.

Dr. Kardina binti Kamaruddin

Email: kardina@kedah.uitm.edu.my (Contact No:+604 - 456 2000)

Skills

Microsoft Excel	Microsoft Words	Microsoft Power Point
Microsoft Publisher	Microsoft Outlook	Photoscape
Paint	E-Perolehan System	Ubs Accounting
Html Notepad	Moviemaker Software	Coral Software
Pdf	Fast Typing Skills 60 Words Per Minutes	E-Perolehan
Autocount Accounting Software		

Language

Language	Strength
English	Good
Bahasa Malaysia	Good
Chinese	Average